[
    {
      "id": 1,
      "question": "Which one of these is not from dc comics?",
      "answer": ["Batman", "Superman", "Ant-man", "Flash"],
      "correctAnswer": "Ant-man",
      "answered": false
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "question": "Which one of these is not from marval comics?",
        "answer": ["Deadpool", "Cyborg", "Hulk", "X-Men"],
        "correctAnswer": "Cyborg",
      "answered": false
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "question": "Which one of these heroes can fly?",
      "answer": ["Thor", "Aquaman", "Spider-Man", "Wolverine"],
      "correctAnswer": "Thor",
      "answered": false
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "question": "What does Billie Batson say in order to run into?",
     "answer": ["I am Groot", "Wassssuuup", "Hickory Dickory Dock", "Shazam"],
      "correctAnswer": "Shazam",
      "answered": false
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "question": "Who has radioactive blood?",
      "answer": ["Spider-Man", "Hulk", "Deadpool", "Superman"],
      "correctAnswer": "Spider-Man",
      "answered": false
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "question": "Which hero did not lose his parents at an early age?",
      "answer": ["Iron Man", "Daredevil", "Batman", "Thor"],
      "correctAnswer": "Thor",
      "answered": false
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "question": "Which one of these newspapers is not real in the superhero universe?",
      "answer": ["Daily Bugle", "Gotham Gazette", "Daily Planet", "Cornwood Times"],
      "correctAnswer": "Cornwood Times",
      "answered": false
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "question": "Who was the earliest popular superhero?",
      "answer": ["Mandrake the Magician", "Batman", "Superman", "The Human Torch"],
      "correctAnswer": "Mandrake the Magician",
      "answered": false
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
      "question": "Who is the most powerful female superhero?",
      "answer": ["Super Girl", "Rogue", "Captain Marvel", "Wonder Woman"],
      "correctAnswer": "Wonder Woman",
      "answered": false
    },
    {
      "id": 10,
      "question": "Which hero was a star quarterback at Gotham University?",
        "answer": ["Booster Gold", "Nightwing", "Blue Beetle", "Red Arrow"],
        "correctAnswer": "Booster Gold",
      "answered": false
    }
  ]
  